We must understand the whole...
That's right, you know, but I thought we were here just for your tonics.
Just give us the voice, too.
Hmm, I know just the tonics you need.
Oh, no.
Your tonics are...
We've got the tonics!
Yay!
What's your voice, Miss?
We can get back to you.
I just want to remind us, okay?
I just want to remind us.
I just want to remind us that, you know, we get 24 hours.
We get 24 hours to revel.
That's it.
We get 24 hours.
Because it doesn't change anything.
And even folks saying he will rise again like Bebe did, I still haven't seen Bebe rise.
I haven't seen Bebe in any normal situations.
The way that you all refer to news outlets as if they are reliable is honestly bizarre to me.
I don't, I don't, I don't understand.
Why, why?
Donald Trump was rushed to Walter Reed Hospital today.
Okay?
So, we get 24 hours to just revel in the passage.
By the way, it doesn't change anything.
I just want to remind us.
Okay?
He's not playing the system.
He is the system.
And, uh, again, I don't by any means believe that Benjamin Netanyahu is alive.
Like, I listened to a segment from the Joe Budden show where I watched five men of various backgrounds argue in defense of capitalism today.
And it just reminded me that, you know, I'm in this bubble with y'all where we understand on a basic level that the system of capitalism is harmful.
Period.
So, like, to watch five men stand on this and earnestly debate from, from a good place, like, they were debating from a good place that capitalism is good, was like, how, how can you, so, no, of course, Mark wasn't.
And Mark was the one telling them capitalism is inherently bad.
So, it was like, and, like, none of their arguments were really strong.
There's, because there's no strong argument to make in defense of capitalism.
Um, I don't need to go on the Joe Budden show to school them.
Mark Lamont Hill is there every day.
And BDOT, who is one of the greatest losers of all time, is now there.
So, it's going to be even more ridiculous.
Because that's a corny, trifling nigga.
Woo-chow, man.
And I feel like, you know, um, it's sad to watch people that I came up with in hip-hop journalism, like, try to just create a semblance of relevance with just being the lowest common denominator.
Um, so, you know, just, it's sad.
Oh.
But shout to Mona and Mark, because those are my peoples.
Um, so, yeah, I just wanted to pop in to remind everybody to send out a prayer, a bismalata, make dua, that, uh, the ancestors dua what they need to.
Roxane Gay simped for kings on threads.
I, I don't.
Mark doesn't need to be surrounded by intellectuals.
Mark is an intellectual.
Mark is in that space so that you all are not watching something that has millions of listeners continue without having an actual influence of intellect in it.
He's, like, doing a public service, so to speak.
Yeah.
So, just wanna have a collective.
Just a collective.
Now, I, I told you he wasn't gonna make it out of this year.
I told y'all that, okay?
I told y'all that the orange one wasn't gonna make it out of this year.
I actually thought it would have been last year, but I knew he wasn't gonna make it out of this year.
We not even, we not even halfway through.
So, let's see.
So, light your white candles.
And, um, I don't know why you guys tell me to come through the pod.
Like, I'm not calling Joe Budden to be, like, hey, can I come on your podcast?
Like, that's not a thing I'm, like, I'm not, I'm not calling anybody, really, and being, like, hey, can I come on your podcast?
Like, unless they're, like, people that I consider to be, like, um, I don't even know, like, I'm not promoting anything per se.
So, like, why, you know?
So, like, that's not how that's gonna go.
Also, like, I don't think that the people on there want to have a genuine, I don't think most of the men on there want to be able to have a genuine conversation.
I also would not ever put myself in a room with BDOT because I would feel the, the degrees that I put so much time and energy into on my wall burst into flames.
And I would come home to the kindling of my house fall into ashes.
So, and now you're saying something to me about Shay Shay, which was two years ago.
So, I, I, I'm not really sure where you guys find it impossible to identify someone's growth.
But it is something you should, um, commit yourself to.
Because you would want someone to identify your growth as well.
Yeah.
So, that's how I feel about that.
That's how I feel about that.
So, with that being said, um, oh my god, you all be asking the dumbest questions about the dumbest people.
And I have no clue.
And honestly, because you all keep asking me that dumb question, that's actually one of the reasons why I am committing myself to doing music.
Because I am so tired of even being thought of in the same context as a terrible grifter, evil idiot.
Like, like the fact that you all would even think of me when you think of her is like beyond me.
Okay?
So, I'm, I'm gonna go back to watching K-pop Demon Hunters.
And I'm gonna bid you all a great evening.
And let's hope that when we wake up tomorrow morning, that we have a new holiday.
Deuces.
That's salad.